Curriculum Vitae

Felicity Walker

4

Birmingham



+44 (0)7493 038 371



Flick walker@hotmail.com

Profile:

An experienced IT professional with a detail oriented and organised approach to tasks. Lead and contributed to large scale (1000+ users) deployments. ITIL v4 Create, Deliver & Support Specialist qualified and experienced in problem management, project management and change management; with focus on compliance and security. Recently completed a Data Academy course covering Python, data visualisation, R and machine learning.

Employment:

University of Worcester 1st Line ICT Service Desk Supervisor

October 2018 – PRESENT

Managed the IT Service Desk functions including telephone, remote support and walk-up desks which supported staff, students and guests. This role has a strong emphasis on process management, reporting and adhering to service based SLAs and KPI's, and producing statistical reports against these. Whilst also having a technical element of organising yearly imaging projects for educational departments and students.

Key successes:

- Implemented processes in line with ITIL, for example virus incidents where no formal process existed, and spotting gaps in existing processes where they didn't work in day-today practice. For example improving the compromised account process so accounts are dealt with in a timely manner and managed so the user understood the severity and implications for the University.
- Drove continual service improvement through service reviews, which fed into incident and request management via the ITSM solution Sysaid.
- Improved customer service by implementing an IP telephony system for the Service Desk to enable better quality of service via 'round robin' call distribution, and introduced KPI's for capacity management.
- Removed the Triage function which bottle necked service requests and incidents, which improved resolution time.
- Lead multiple projects such as a new departmental website and Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG 2.1) project, to make use of the O365 Suite on how to produce accessible documents for teaching and assist the disability and dyslexia support team in replacing additional software with O365, thus saving on licence fees.
- Introduced OLAs with other University support teams that the IT Service Desk answer queries on, to better manage customer expectations.
- Currently implementing a new ITSM solution and improving on the existing solution Sysaid until implemented. Improving the user self-service portal by transferring the OneNote knowledge base into Sysaid to help users answer their own questions.
- Improved IT communications via the IT status page tool to ensure all communications displayed a consistent message.
- Improved the team as a whole to better understand why IT does things in certain way by educating
 them from my SDI Service Desk Analyst course to improve problem management identification and
 drive incident management identification. As well as educating them on change management to
 drive incident management.

Employment:

DWF LLP
IT Technician

February 2018 - October 2018

Co-ordinated support for the local and other international offices. In this role I utilized my project management experience ensuring projects were deployed in a timely manner. I gained further in depth experience with technologies such as Azure, Active Directory, SCCM and Exchange. Always taking a detail oriented approach to incidents and problems.

Employment: (Continued)

Key successes:

- Undertook system administration for new users and leavers.
- Tackled tech alignment projects, with my project management skills ensuring all users had the correct software and hardware. And the correct testing had be undertaken by myself and others for Office 365 and Visual Files role outs.
- Conducted server audits to support the ISO accreditation.
- Developed in depth knowledge about SCCM deployment, troubleshooting and reporting, for build and release issues.

Gowling WLG (UK) LLP SUBJECT MATTER ANALYST

SEPTEMBER 2015 – February 2018

Co-ordinating mobile device management, I liaised with all levels of the business from Partners to international offices. In this role I transitioned from an IT General Analyst, to a Mobile Device Manager and Specialist, developing my skills with mobile device management integrations and with focus on.

Key successes:

- Strong 3rd party supplier management skills, being a key contributor to decisions with AirWatch, Vodafone and future conferencing services, Zoom. Undertaking procurement processes for new contracts, renewals and mobile budgets. Always ensuring projects stuck to tight deadlines.
- Started the transition and migration from AirWatch to BB UEM, including scoping. Ensuring it was planned effectively for a smooth delivery, involving device selection and testing so devices where up to spec and usable from a consumer perspective.
- Improved the mobile device estate, by ensuring user information was accurate and up to date, which
 saved money on active connections and that all devices were auditable by introducing a database on
 ServiceNow. I further developed ServiceNow with the ServiceNow developer to create a mobile loan
 system.
- Continually promoted the work of the department at many internal events for Gowling WLG, including the Partners Conference and new starter events.
- Gained my ITIL qualification and completed subsequent courses on problem management, project management; to ensure proactive monitoring to anticipate any issues.
- Introduced technology such as Apple DEP to manage operating system upgrades. Whilst I also conducted product reviews such as Wandera.
- In this role I continually developed the out-sourced service desk, conducting training sessions with focus on their development to improve service delivery.
- Always ensured client security for the firm through the implementation of Blancco, whilst supporting security accreditations and client security audits.
- Managed office moves which always ran smoothly, due to my keen eye for detail.

Education:

Liverpool John Moores University

2010-2013

2:1/ Psychology

My degree enabled me to bring a lot of transferable skills to my professional career. Through conducting research studies at university, my strong research and analytical skills have provided me the insight to take a methodical approach to incidents, problem management, testing and projects. By having to stick to deadlines at university this offers a perspective in my work to manage time and workload efficiently and effectively. Because of this, my ability to absorb and learn from information quickly has been a big key to my success in the technology sector. Thus, showcasing my adaptability and versatility, through critical observation.

Ounsdale High School and Sixth Form

2002-2009

- 3 A-Levels in Psychology, English language and literature, Politics
- 5 + GCSE including B's in Maths, Science and English